# **NWAGBOO JOHN**

#### **Front End Developer**

#### **Personal Details**

Address: 8, Olaide Adekoya Street, Kudeyibu Estate, Ijegun-Ikotun, Lagos.

Email: nemejohn62@gmail.com

**Phone:** 09118166827

#### **Education**

High school diploma

Towab Private Collage, Ijegun 2016-2023

### **Training**

Fliptotech Training academy
2023 – present

#### Skills

HTML/CSS - Intermediate

JavaScript - Intermediate

Web-design - Intermediate

UI/UX - Intermediate

Graphics Design - Intermediate

## **Summary**

Frontend developer, UI/UX designer and Web Designer with three months of experience working with javaScript HTML/CSS, Webflow and Figma, Passionate to deliver and develop applications and experiences on the web to client satisfaction. With good knowledge of coding specialized in creating exceptional, current and responsive websites.

## **Experience**

## **Front End Developer**

September 2023 - Present

- Developed front-end user interface for several complex web applications with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Collaborated with web designers and back-end developers to ensure we application met customer requirements.
- Partnered with data science to develop the front-end for a product recommendation engine that increased user time on a page by 5 minutes.

## **Front End Web Designer**

September 2023 - Present

- Designing personalize website for fresher, middle and senior level clients.
- Modifying and making changes according to client's requirements.
- After the client approve the design, then the next step was to create the live website.
- Making the website responsive.

### **UI/UX Designer**

September 2023 - Present

- Designing amemable and flexible websites
- UI/UX designer with passion for designing beautiful and functional interface

#### Reference:

Mr. Ola: Senior Frontend Developer

Tel: 07052490998